[Show Ads](javascript:showAds())

[Hide Ads](javascript:hideAds())  

Privacy Statement for mathsisfun.com
====================================

Also Read: [Internet Safety Guide](https://www.mathsisfun.com/internet-safety.html)

### Overview

Mathsisfun.com does not have memberships or subscriptions, and **does not keep any personally identifiable information** (except what you say when you [contact us](https://www.mathsisfun.com/contact.php)).

We use "cookies" to store some settings such as when you click "Hide Ads". Advertisers may also use information about you that is out of our control.

Here are the details:

_This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for mathsisfun.com, and advises you of what information may be collected via this website and what will happen to it._

* _What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site_
* _The organization collecting the information_
* _How the information is used_
* _With whom the information may be shared_
* _What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information_
* _The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under mathsisfun.com control_
* _How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information._

**_If you feel that we are not abiding by our privacy policy, please [contact us](https://www.mathsisfun.com/contact.php)  
  
_**

Information Collection and Use
------------------------------

Mathsisfun.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Mathsisfun.com collects only enough information to provide basic functionality and security.

Cookies
-------

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer containing information about the user's visit. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the site can know if you pressed "hide ads". If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site.

Advertisers
-----------

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Log Files
---------

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

Links to Other Sites
--------------------

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that mathsisfun.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Security
--------

Mathsisfun.com is a free information-only service and sells no products directly. At no time will mathsisfun.com directly request address or payment details. However, some partner sites do sell direct. Please check as mathsisfun.com cannot be responsible for insecure transactions from other web sites.

Notification of Changes
-----------------------

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will notify users on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

Last Updated: Tuesday 10 Mar 2019

Copyright © 2019 MathsIsFun.com
